# BRAMANTYO ARYO WICAKSONO

bram.antyo2796@gmail.com | +6281331892338 | Special Region of Yogyakarta, Indonesia 55571 www.linkedin.com/in/bram-a-061a00284

#### SUMMARY

5 years and 5 month total experience from junior engineering into software engineering with speciality in Magento 2 Back End. Abble toeffectively self-manage during independent projectas well good people management by adapting to new technology environment.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **ICUBE BY SIRCLO**

May 2019 - Present

- Developed new features, enhancements, and ensured code quality and timely delivery.
- Managed maintenance, bug fixing, and system stability.
- Provided backup support for leads and mentored junior engineers.
- Resolved issues and upgraded Magento 2 projects for better performance.
- Led server migrations and ensured seamless transitions.
- Maintained systems and improved user experience through new features.
- Creating apps on Shopify with Laravel, n8n, RabbitMQ.

# **Freelance Software Engineer**

Jan 2022 - Feb 2024

- Creating request for customize module for 3rd services and restriction features using Magento 2.4.5 .
- Develop projects for manage student's academic record using Code Igniter.
- Develop projects for manage document and tracking ship for mining company using Laravel.

## **PT Time Excelindo**

Jan 2017 - May 2017

- Performed comprehensive manual testing to ensure product quality and functionality.
- · Created detailed user manuals and documentation to guide users through software features.

# **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Computer Science**

Aug 2014 - Nov 2018

- University of Duta Wacana Christian
- · Major in Information System.
- Final CGPA: 3.05

# **CERTIFICATIONS** PHPProgramming Certificate

May 2023

DTA-23-00406

PHP Programming Certificate - DTA-23-00406

### **KEY SKILLS**

- PHP
- Css
- Java
- Github
- GitLab
- GraphQl

MySql

- API

- Magento 2
- Laravel
- Code Igniter
- Woocommerce
- Shopify
- · Problem Solving.
- Maintenance.
- · Creating Features.
- Communicative in English.
- Fluent in Bahasa.
- Corporate Communication.